Norman Vincent Peale Papers
Norman Vincent Peale Papers
- I. Correspondence
  - B: Special correspondence
    - Norman Vincent Peale correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1952
        - Advertising (Metropolitan Advertising Co.), 1956-1959 (Box I:B:86)
        - Albany, Georgia (Box I:B:87)
        - Alexander, Phyllis (Box I:B:87)
        - Alpha Delta (Box I:B:87)
        - Amazing Results of Positive Thinking (Box I:B:87)
        - American Colony Charities Association (Bertha Spafford Vester) (Box I:B:87)
        - American Foundation of Religion and Psychiatry
          - Development Committee Correspondence (Box I:B:87)
          - Record of Contribution (Box I:B:87)
          - Reports, Minutes, Literature (Box I:B:88)
          - Staff Correspondence (Box I:B:88)
        - American Schools and Colleges Association - Kenneth J. Beebe (Horatio Alger Awards) (Box I:B:88)
        - Anderson, South Carolina (Box I:B:89)
        - Arnaz, Mr. and Mrs. Desi (Box I:B:89)
        - Articles and Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box I:B:89)
        - Authorized Quotations for Publication (Box I:B:89)
        - Autograph Requests (Box I:B:89)
        - Awards (Box I:B:89)
        - Bay, Mrs. Charles Ulrick (Box I:B:90)
        - Bennett, Milliard (Box I:B:90)
        - Bering, A.L. (Box I:B:90)
        - Bible Story Book (Box I:B:90)
        - Blanton, Smiley (Box I:B:90)
        - Books for Dr. Peale, 1953-1955 (Box I:B:90)
        - Book Acknowledgements (Box I:B:91)
        - Broadcasting and Film Commission (Box I:B:91)
        - Broadcasting and Film commissions, weekly sermons (Box I:B:91)
        - Brother Andrews (Box I:B:92)
        - Burman, Roger (Box I:B:92)
        - CBS (Box I:B:92)
        - Chicago, 1954-1959 (Box I:B:92)
        - Christian Freedom Foundation (Box I:B:93)
        - Christian Herald (Box I:B:93)
        - Church Calendars (Box I:B:93)
        - Classis (Box I:B:93)
        - Cleveland (Box I:B:93)
        - Clippings (newspaper) (Box I:B:93)
        - Collegiate Church Correspondence (Box I:B:93)
        - Collegiate Church Ministers (Romig, Palen, Poling) (Box I:B:93)
        - Collegiate Church Reports (Box I:B:93)
        - Financial Report, 1953; 1955-1956 (Box I:B:94)
        - Columbus, Georgia (Box I:B:94)
        - Columbus, Ohio (Box I:B:94)
        - Coming of the King (Box I:B:94)
        - Commission to Study Evangelism (Box I:B:94)
        - Committee of One Million (Box I:B:95)
        - "Confident Living" (Box I:B:95)
        - "Confident Living", correspondence (Box I:B:95)
        - "Confident Living", column on fraternity boys (Box I:B:95)
        - Consistory, correspondence, reports (Box I:B:95)
        - Contracts (Box I:B:95)
        - Cross Reference (Box I:B:95)
        - Dallas, Texas (Box I:B:96)
        - Decatur, Illinois (Box I:B:96)
        - Detroit, Michigan (Box I:B:96)
        - Dickler, Gerald (Box I:B:96)
        - Dictaphone Corporation (Carol Lyttle) (Box I:B:96)
        - Doeskin (Box I:B:96)
        - Edelstein Record Project (Box I:B:96)
        - Faith at Work (Irving Harris) (Box I:B:97)
        - F.B.I. (Box I:B:97)
        - Fifield, James W. Jr. (Box I:B:97)
        - Florida, general, Miami and Miami Beach (Box I:B:97)
        - Florida, misc. (maps, printed matter, etc.), property, correspondence (Box I:B:98)
        - Foreign
          - Africa, Austria, Australia (Box I:B:98)
          - Automobiles (Box I:B:99)
          - Belgium (Box I:B:99)
          - Bermuda and Nassau (Box I:B:99)
          - Bon Voyage Messages (Box I:B:99)
          - Canada (Box I:B:99)
          - Denmark (Box I:B:99)
          - Egypt (Box I:B:99)
          - England (Box I:B:99)
          - Formosa II - France (Box I:B:100)
          - General (Maps, Pictures, Travel Folders, Etc.) (Box I:B:100)
          - General (Box I:B:100)
          - Germany (Box I:B:100)
          - Hawaii (Honolulu), Manila (Philippines) (Box I:B:101)
          - Hong Kong, Taiwan and China (Box I:B:101)
          - Holland (Box I:B:101)
          - Italy (Box I:B:101)
          - Japan (Box I:B:101)
          - Near East (Greece, Jerusalem, Lebanon, Palestine, Saudi Arabia, Syria) (Box I:B:101)
          - Scotland (Box I:B:101)
          - Norway (Box I:B:101)
          - Spain - Sweden (Box I:B:101)
          - Switzerland (Box I:B:101)
          - Travel Bureaus (Box I:B:102)
        - Fort Lauderdale, Florida (Box I:B:102)
        - Foundation for Christian Living (Box I:B:102)
        - F.R.A.S.C.D. (Charles Wesley Lowry) (Box I:B:102)
        - French, George (Box I:B:103)
        - Gainfort, John (Box I:B:103)
        - Giniger, Kenneth S. (Box I:B:103)
        - Girls' Town (Box I:B:103)
        - Gordon, Arthur (Box I:B:103)
        - Graham, Billy (Box I:B:103)
        - Gregory, Jasper (Box I:B:103)
        - Guideposts
          - Articles, Dr. and Mrs. Peale (Box I:B:103)
          - Bank Balance Statements (Box I:B:104)
          - John Beach (Box I:B:104)
          - William Boal (Box I:B:104)
          - Board of Directors (Box I:B:104)
          - Editorial Office (Box I:B:104)
          - Financial (Box I:B:104)
          - Guideposts Foundation
            - Rose Weiss (Box I:B:105)
            - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box I:B:105)
            - Investments Account, 1954-1959 (Box I:B:105)
            - Investment Account (Box I:B:106)
            - Len Le Sourd (Box I:B:106)
            - Loomis Sayles Investment Reports (Box I:B:106)
            - Operations (Box I:B:106)
          - Promotion (Box I:B:107)
          - Nelson Rector (Box I:B:107)
          - Alan Reid (Box I:B:107)
          - William Stafford (Box I:B:107)
          - Television (Box I:B:107)
        - Hall Syndicate Correspondence (Box I:B:107)
        - Hall Syndicate Statements (Box I:B:107)
        - Hallmark Cards (Box I:B:108)
        - Hallmark Correspondence (Box I:B:108)
        - Harrisburg, PA (Box I:B:108)
        - Heard, Paul (Box I:B:108)
        - High, Stanley (Box I:B:108)
        - I.C.R. Movie (Millard Bennett) (Box I:B:109)
        - Insurance (Box I:B:109)
        - Interesting Letters (Box I:B:109)
        - Invitations (Box I:B:109)
        - Iowa Wesleyan (Box I:B:109)
        - Itineraries, 1953-? (Box I:B:109)
        - Kingston, NY (Box I:B:109)
        - Kresge, Stanley S. (Box I:B:109)
        - Kridel, Frank W. (Box I:B:110)
        - Le Sourd, Howard M. (Box I:B:110)
        - Len Le Sourd (Box I:B:110)
        - Lieb, Clarence (Box I:B:110)
        - Look
          - Articles (Box I:B:110)
          - William Arthur (Box I:B:110)
          - Contract (Box I:B:110)
          - General Correspondence (Box I:B:111)
          - Mr. Eliott - Lookletters, 1954-1955 (Box I:B:111)
          - Misc. (Reports, Clippings,Etc.) (Box I:B:111)
          - S.O. Shapiro (Box I:B:111)
        - Loomis Sayles (Floyd L. McElroy) (Box I:B:111)
        - Los Angeles (Box I:B:112)
        - Marble Church
          - Budget (Box I:B:112)
          - Elders and Deacons (Box I:B:112)
          - Misc. (Box I:B:112)
          - Organizations, 1954-1959 (Box I:B:112)
        - Marble Church Staff
          - Herman L. Barberry (Box I:B:113)
          - Mary Brining and Lyn Bonneville (Box I:B:113)
          - Burrill, Cronham, Fielding (Box I:B:113)
          - Groll, Hoffman, Jones (Box I:B:113)
          - Juergens (Box I:B:113)
          - Mary Creighton (Box I:B:113)
          - Doris Phillips (Box I:B:113)
          - Eugene M. Pierce (Box I:B:113)
          - Isabell Sacre (Box I:B:113)
          - Shay, Shindell, Van Buren (Box I:B:113)
        - Marble Times, 1957 (Box I:B:113)
        - Marble Times, 1958 (Box I:B:114)
        - Masterwork Treasury (Box I:B:114)
        - Material Sent, 1954 (Box I:B:114)
        - Matsumoto, Toru (Box I:B:114)
        - Mattern, H.C. and Mary (Box I:B:114)
        - Correspondence returned by Mrs. Peale; McCall mail; some question letters, 1954 (Box I:B:114)
        - McElroy, Floyd L. (Box I:B:115)
        - Memphis, Tenn. (Box I:B:115)
        - Metropolitan Club (Box I:B:115)
        - Mills, Charles B. (Box I:B:115)
        - Miscellaneous (Box I:B:115)
        - Monahan, James (Box I:B:115)
        - Music Scores and Manuscripts (Box I:B:115)
        - NBC Question and Answer Program (Box I:B:115)
        - NBC Question and Answer Program Correspondence (Box I:B:116)
        - NBC Staff Correspondence (Box I:B:116)
        - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box I:B:116)
        - National Council of Churches, Committee on Evangelism:
          - Staff Correspondence (Box I:B:116)
          - World Study (Box I:B:116)
          - Conference on Red China (Box I:B:116)
        - Ohio Friends (Box I:B:116)
        - Ohio Society (Box I:B:116)
        - Ohio Wesleyan University Correspondence (Box I:B:117)
        - Ohio Wesleyan Reports (Box I:B:117)
        - Oursler, Mrs. Fulton (Box I:B:117)
        - Owens, Gerald (Box I:B:117)
        - Peale, Dr. and Mrs. C.C. (Box I:B:117)
        - Peale, Charles, Eva and Lucy (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, Elizabeth (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, John (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, Leonard D. (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, Louise (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, Margaret (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, Birthday, 1959 (Box I:B:118)
        - N.V.P. Biography - Crisis on N.V.P. (Box I:B:118)
        - Peale, N.V.
          - Boyhood Experiences (Box I:B:118)
          - Engagement and Memos (Box I:B:118)
          - Peale Genealogy (Box I:B:118)
          - General Memos (Box I:B:119)
          - Gordon Biography, Minister to Millions (Box I:B:119)
          - 25th Anniversary Marble Church (Box I:B:119)
          - Misc.(Quotes, Criticisms, Favorites, Etc.) (Box I:B:119)
          - Summer Correspondence (Box I:B:120)
          - Silver Wedding Anniversary (Box I:B:120)
        - Peale, Mrs. N.V., general memos (Box I:B:120)
        - Peale, Robert C. (Box I:B:120)
        - Peale, Robert W. (Box I:B:120)
        - Peale, William (Box I:B:120)
        - Peat, Mrs. Harold (Box I:B:120)
        - Pees, O.W. (Box I:B:120)
        - Phi Gamma Delta, general (Box I:B:121)
        - Phi Gamma Delta, C.J. (Scoop) Wilkinson (Box I:B:121)
        - Philadelphia, PA (Box I:B:121)
        - Pittsburg, PA Allegheny Memorial Cemetery (Box I:B:121)
        - Poling, Daniel A. (Box I:B:121)
        - Power of Positive Thinking (Box I:B:121)
        - Power of Positive Thinking for Young People (Box I:B:121)
        - Amazing Results of Positive Thinking, Requests for Permission to Quote (Box I:B:122)
        - Power of Positive Thinking, book testimonials (Box I:B:122)
        - Power of Positive Thinking, publicity (Box I:B:122)
        - Prentice-Hall
          - Bible Stories (Box I:B:122)
          - Boardman, Myron L. (Box I:B:122)
          - Christie, L.H. (Box I:B:122)
          - Misc. (Box I:B:122)
          - Royalty Statements (Box I:B:123)
          - Thayer, Marjorie (Box I:B:123)
        - Presbrey-Leland (Box I:B:123)
        - Presbyterian Ministers' Fund (Box I:B:123)
        - Protestant Council (Box I:B:123)
        - Rapport, Dr. Albert (Box I:B:123)
        - Readers Digest (Box I:B:123)
        - Readers Digest, reader response on immortality article (Box I:B:124)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:124)
        - Rotary Club of New York (Box I:B:124)
        - Rumely, Edward A. (Box I:B:124)
        - St. Louis, MO Chamber of Commerce (Box I:B:124)
        - San Francisco (Box I:B:124)
        - San Francisco Speech Requests (Box I:B:125)
        - Salescience (Box I:B:125)
        - Seventeen East 84th St. (Box I:B:125)
        - Sheppard, Russell (Box I:B:125)
        - Shoemaker, Dr. Samuel (Box I:B:125)
        - Stafford, miscellaneous (Box I:B:125)
        - Sneed, Dr. J. Richard (Box I:B:125)
        - Shrine (Box I:B:125)
        - Sons of the American Revolution (Box I:B:125)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-H (Box I:B:126)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, I-T (Box I:B:127)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, U-Z (Box I:B:128)
        - Spratt, Elliot J. (Box I:B:128)
        - Stafford, Charles M. (Box I:B:128)
        - Stafford, Frank (Box I:B:128)
        - Stafford, William (Box I:B:128)
        - Stay Alive All Your Life (Box I:B:128)
        - N.V.P. Summer (Box I:B:128)
        - N.V.P. Special, Summer Supply, 1959 (Box I:B:128)
        - Summer Supply Ministers, 1954-1959 (Box I:B:129)
        - Summer 1959, Travel and Hotel (Box I:B:129)
        - Switzerland Correspondence, 1956 (Box I:B:129)
        - Syndicated Columns, Post Hall Offer, 1959 (Box I:B:129)
        - 1025 Fifth Ave. (Box I:B:130)
        - 1030 Fifth Ave. (Box I:B:130)
        - Testimonial Letters (Box I:B:130)
        - Thomas, Lowell (Box I:B:130)
        - Union League Club (Box I:B:130)
        - Volk, Kurt H. (Box I:B:130)
        - Ward, Bishop Ralph A. (Box I:B:130)
        - Washington D.C. (Box I:B:130)
        - Washington and Lee University (Box I:B:130)
        - What's Your Trouble? (Box I:B:130)
        - Washington Square Park (Box I:B:130)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1962
        - Advertising (Box I:B:131)
        - Alexander Phyllis (Box I:B:131)
        - Alpha Delta (Box I:B:131)
        - Amazing Results (Box I:B:131)
        - American Colony (Box I:B:131)
        - American Schools and Colleges - Horatio Alger (Box I:B:131)
        - A.F.R.A.P.
          - Reports, Minutes, Literature (Box I:B:131)
          - Staff Correspondence (Box I:B:132)
          - Stone, W. Clement (Box I:B:132)
        - Anonymous (Box I:B:132)
        - Art of Living Appeal Letters (Box I:B:132)
        - Art of Living, 1960 (Box I:B:132)
        - Area Work (Box I:B:132)
        - Atlanta, Georgia (Box I:B:132)
        - Atlantic City, New Jersey (Box I:B:133)
        - Ball, Lucille (Box I:B:133)
        - Beach, John (Box I:B:133)
        - Bennett, Millard (Box I:B:133)
        - Bering, A.L. (Box I:B:133)
        - Birthday Greetings, 1962 (Box I:B:133)
        - Blanton, Dr .Smiley (Box I:B:133)
        - Books, Acknowledged (Box I:B:133)
        - Bridgeport, Conn. (Box I:B:133)
        - Broadcasting and Films (Box I:B:134)
        - Charlestown, West Virginia (Box I:B:134)
        - Christian Freedoms Foundation (Box I:B:134)
        - Christian Herald (Box I:B:134)
        - Cincinnati, Ohio (Box I:B:134)
        - Classis (Box I:B:134)
        - Collegiate Church correspondence, Ministers, Reports, Etc. (Box I:B:134)
        - "Confident Living" (Box I:B:135)
        - Committee One Million (Box I:B:135)
        - Consistory (Box I:B:135)
        - Contracts (Box I:B:135)
        - Corpus Christi, Texas (Box I:B:135)
        - Correspondence (Box I:B:135)
        - Crank Mail (Box I:B:135)
        - Criticism (Box I:B:135)
        - Dallas, Texas (Box I:B:135)
        - Dickler, Gerald (Box I:B:135)
        - Dictaphone, Corp. (Box I:B:135)
        - Easter Offering, 1962 (Box I:B:135)
        - Mr. and Mrs. Paul Everett
          - Thank You Letters and Wedding Pictures and Clippings (Box I:B:135)
          - Wedding Invitation List (Box I:B:136)
        - Excerpts (Box I:B:136)
        - Faith at Work (Box I:B:136)
        - Fawcett publication (Box I:B:136)
        - F.B.I. (Box I:B:136)
        - Fifield, James W. (Box I:B:136)
        - Foreign (general), maps, pictures, travel folders (Box I:B:136)
        - Foreign
          - Austria (Box I:B:136)
          - Australia (Box I:B:136)
          - Denmark (Box I:B:136)
          - Egypt (Box I:B:136)
          - England (Box I:B:136)
          - Formosa (Box I:B:136)
          - France (Box I:B:137)
          - Germany (Box I:B:137)
          - Hawaii (Box I:B:137)
          - Holland (Box I:B:137)
          - Hong Kong, Taiwan, China (Box I:B:137)
          - Ireland and N. Ireland (Box I:B:137)
          - Italy (Box I:B:137)
          - Japan (Box I:B:137)
          - Near East (Box I:B:137)
          - Scotland (Box I:B:137)
          - Switzerland (Box I:B:138)
        - Special FCL (Box I:B:138)
        - Foundation for Christian Living (Box I:B:138)
        - FRASCO Charles W. Lowry (Box I:B:138)
        - George French (Box I:B:138)
        - French Lick, Indiana (Box I:B:138)
        - Girls' Town (Box I:B:139)
        - GP [ Guideposts?]
          - Articles (Box I:B:139)
          - Board of Directors (Box I:B:139)
          - Editorial Office (Box I:B:139)
          - Financial (Box I:B:139)
          - General (Box I:B:139)
          - General Correspondence (Box I:B:139)
          - Hallmark Cards (Box I:B:139)
          - Hallmark Correspondence (Box I:B:139)
          - Operations (Box I:B:139)
          - Reports and Leonard Peak Correspondence (Box I:B:139)
          - Arthur Gordon (Box I:B:139)
        - Gregory, Jasper (Box I:B:140)
        - Guideposts
          - William Boal (Box I:B:140)
          - Irving Granville (Box I:B:140)
          - Charles Kerward (Box I:B:140)
          - Leu Le Sourd (Box I:B:140)
          - Loomis-Sayles (Box I:B:140)
          - Nelson, Rector (Box I:B:140)
          - Rose Weiss (Box I:B:140)
          - Alfred P. Haak (Box I:B:140)
        - Hall Syndicate (Box I:B:141)
        - Hall Syndicate Statements (Box I:B:141)
        - Heard, Paul (Box I:B:141)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:141)
        - Keyes (Box I:B:141)
        - Le Tourneau (Box I:B:141)
        - Menninger (Box I:B:141)
        - Stengel (Box I:B:141)
        - Industrial-Pastoral Counseling (Box I:B:141)
        - Jackson, Mississippi (Box I:B:142)
        - Kresge, Stanley S. (Box I:B:142)
        - Layton, William P. (Box I:B:142)
        - LeSourd, Howard M. (Box I:B:142)
        - Lieb, Clarence (Box I:B:142)
        - Los Angeles, CA (Box I:B:142)
        - Marble Church
          - Advisory Committee (Box I:B:142)
          - Area Work Budget (Box I:B:142)
          - Budget, 1962 (Box I:B:142)
          - Budget, Passing Folder (Box I:B:142)
        - Marble Church Cronlarn Choir (Box I:B:143)
        - Marble Collegiate Church
          - Elders and Deacons (Box I:B:143)
          - Don Hoffman (Box I:B:143)
          - Louise Kay (Box I:B:143)
          - Minister's Reports (Herman L. Barbery, Don Hoffman, E.M. Pierce) (Box I:B:143)
          - Misc. (Box I:B:143)
          - New Members (Box I:B:143)
          - Audrey O'Connor (Box I:B:143)
          - Organizations, B and P. (Box I:B:143)
          - Robert Owens (Box I:B:143)
          - E.M. Pierce (Box I:B:143)
          - Bell Sacre (Box I:B:143)
          - Mary Brivig (Box I:B:143)
          - Mary Ireighton (Box I:B:143)
          - William Groll (Box I:B:143)
        - Marble Times (Box I:B:144)
        - Marble Church, Wimona Grant (Box I:B:144)
        - Metropolitan Club (Box I:B:144)
        - Mills, Charles B. (Box I:B:144)
        - Mt. Holyoke (Box I:B:144)
        - Mt. Holyoke Parents Committee, 1962 (Box I:B:144)
        - Music Scores and Manuscripts (Box I:B:144)
        - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box I:B:144)
        - National Council of Churches (Box I:B:144)
        - National Council of Churches, B and F Commission (Box I:B:144)
        - National Council of Churche, criticism (Box I:B:144)
        - New Minister West End Church (Box I:B:144)
        - Ohio Society (Box I:B:145)
        - Ohio Wesleyan University Correspondence (Box I:B:145)
        - Panama City, Florida (Box I:B:145)
        - Mrs. Z.Z. Peale (Box I:B:145)
        - Elizabeth Peale (Box I:B:145)
        - John Peale (Box I:B:145)
        - Leonard Peale (Box I:B:145)
        - Margaret Peale Birthday Greetings (Box I:B:145)
        - Mrs. N.V. Peale, memos (Box I:B:145)
        - General Memos (Box I:B:145)
        - Peale, Robert L. (Box I:B:146)
        - Peale, Robert W. (Box I:B:146)
        - Phi Gamma Delta (Box I:B:146)
        - Poling, Daniel A. (Box I:B:146)
        - Power of Positive Thinking (Box I:B:146)
        - Prayer and Sick List (Box I:B:146)
        - Prentice-Hall
          - Misc. (Box I:B:146)
          - Myron Boardman (Box I:B:146)
          - Christie, L.H. (Box I:B:146)
        - Presbyterian Ministers' Fund (Box I:B:146)
        - Protestant Council (Box I:B:147)
        - Readers Digest (Box I:B:147)
        - Reformed Church (Box I:B:147)
        - Requests for Contributions (Box I:B:147)
        - Rexall (Box I:B:147)
        - Ross, Frank (Box I:B:147)
        - Rotary Club (Box I:B:147)
        - Salew, Mohammed (Box I:B:147)
        - Scottish Rite - Shrine (Box I:B:147)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, A-H (Box I:B:148)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, I-Q (Box I:B:149)
        - Speaking Engagements Rejected, R-W (Box I:B:150)
        - Stafford, Charles M. (Box I:B:150)
        - Stafford, William Guideposts (Box I:B:150)
        - Stafford, William (Box I:B:150)
        - Stafford, Misc. (Box I:B:150)
        - Summer Supply (Box I:B:150)
        - Summer Supply (Box I:B:151)
        - Sunday Visitors (Box I:B:151)
        - Television Shipping Lists (Box I:B:151)
        - 1030 Fifth Ave. (Box I:B:151)
        - 30th Anniversary (Box I:B:151)
        - Thomas, Earl G. Record Project (Box I:B:151)
        - Toledo, Ohio (Box I:B:151)
        - "Tough Minded Optimist", critical letters
        - Volk, Kurt H. (Box I:B:151)
        - Walton, New York (Box I:B:151)
        - White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia (Box I:B:151)
        - Wichita, Kansas (Box I:B:151)
        - Wilbur, Ben, TV Project (Box I:B:151)
        - Wilbur, Ben, TV Shipping Lists (Box I:B:151)
    - Joe Levy files
      This file contains correspondence dealing with the Foundation for Christian Living, Presbyterian Ministers Fund, and the 1960 Kennedy Campaign. This file is arranged two ways: one part is listed chronologically, and within the year strictly alphabetically, and the second part is listed chronologically, and within the year, alphabetically by subject.
      - Correspondence, 1960
        - A-Cq (Box I:B:152)
        - Cr-J (Box I:B:153)
        - K-Pd (Box I:B:154)
        - Pe-Z (Box I:B:155)
        - Advertising (Box I:B:156)
        - American Foundation of Religion and Psychiatry (Box I:B:156)
        - Anonymous (Box I:B:156)
        - Birthday (Box I:B:156)
        - Books (Box I:B:156)
        - Broadcasting and Film Commission (Box I:B:156)
        - Building Campaign (Box I:B:156)
        - Collegiate Church (Box I:B:156)
        - Clinic (Box I:B:156)
        - Crank Mail (Box I:B:156)
        - Easter Offering (Box I:B:156)
        - Elders and Deacons (Box I:B:156)
        - Employment (Box I:B:157)
        - Fan Mail (Box I:B:157)
        - Foreign Mail (Box I:B:157)
        - F.C.L. (Box I:B:157)
        - Genealogy (Box I:B:157)
        - Guideposts (Box I:B:157)
        - Illustrations (Box I:B:157)
        - Letters Re: Kennedy Statement, May 1960 (Box I:B:157)
        - Marble Church Form Letter Addressed to Church Members (Box I:B:157)
        - Marble Collegiate Times (Box I:B:157)
        - New Members (Box I:B:157)
        - Poems, Songs, Misc. (Box I:B:157)
        - Political Controversy (Box I:B:157)
        - Prayer and Sick List (Box I:B:157)
        - Prayer Requests (Box I:B:157)
        - Prentice-Hall (Box I:B:157)
        - Presbyterian Ministers' Fund (Box I:B:158)
        - Letters Re: Protestant Statement, May 1960 (Box I:B:158)
        - Problems (Box I:B:159)
        - References (Box I:B:159)
        - Reformed Church in America (Box I:B:159)
        - Requests for Articles Requests for Gifts (Box I:B:159)
        - Rotary Club (Box I:B:159)
        - Sermon Excerpts (Box I:B:159)
        - Vacation and Rest Homes Visitors (Box I:B:159)
        - A-Cn (Box I:B:159)
        - Co-Mc (Box I:B:160)
        - Mi-Z (Box I:B:161)
        - Advertising (Box I:B:162)
        - American Foundation of Religion and Psychology (Box I:B:162)